So we are in the roll your own portion of shotgun.
We've each rolled one card we've had a betting round.
What happens now?
Well we're going to roll another card right?
Player to my left rolls a jack of hearts to match his queen of hearts.
We see what he's trying to sell there right?
He's trying to sell a straight or a flush or a straight flush or a royal flush.
You roll a ten to match your jack which is also the same suit.
You too are trying to sell a straight a flush a straight flush or a royal.
To your left we see again a sales pitch and I roll out a potential straight.
So we're all selling here and considering that these hands are on similar footing I don't think any of us are going away but you should bet and we'll talk more about that in the next segment.